https://www.kenscio.com/privacy-policy

www.kenscio.com
Kenscio has agreed to notify you of:
What personally identifiable information of yours or third party’s is collected from you through the web site
The organization that is collecting the information
How the information is used
With whom the information may be shared
What are the choices available to you with regards to collection, use and distribution of the information
What are the kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information that is under Kenscio’s control
How can you correct any inaccuracies in the information collected
Information collection and use
Any information collected on this site becomes the property of Kenscio. Kenscio will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in any way which is different from what is disclosed in this statement. We collect information from our users at several different points on our website.
Information you upload into Kenscio
Kenscio offers self-service email based direct marketing solutions for small and mid-size businesses. The client data which is uploaded into our system is stored in a secure location. Kenscio does not sell or rent any client data that has been loaded on to our system. Only the registered account holder can gain access to the uploaded lists.
Registration
No registration is required to view the Kenscio website.
Log files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Sharing
We will share average or approximate demographic information with 3rd parties in the case they would like to know demographics of our audience. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We do not share personally identifiable information with 3rd parties.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we at Kenscio are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Kenscio.com
Data security
We take every precaution to protect our users’ information.
When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.
All of our servers are protected by physical and logical firewalls.
Stringent measures are taken to protect user-information off-line.
All of our users’ information is restricted access only.
Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information.
All our employees use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to regain access to protected information.
Furthermore, All employees are updated as to our security and privacy practices.
Every month, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers’ information is protected.
Finally, the physical servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure co-location facility, within locked cages that only Kenscio network administrators have access to.
This facility provides security 24 hours a day, 365 days a year and guarantees our servers against power outages by using automated backup power systems.
Special offers
We send all new members a verification email to verify password and username. Established members who have chosen it receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications.
Administrative Email Communications
You will receive administrative emails that are related to the usage of our service. You may not opt-out of administrative emails. These administrative emails do not have any marketing, promotional or advertising material(s) in them.
Correction/personal Information Update
If your personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if you no longer desire our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update that personal data provided to us. You can do this by calling on telephone number at +91-8042042734 or by sending us an email to Customer Support at enquiries@kenscio.com. If you want your account deactivated please state this in your communication.
Change notifications
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will prominently post those changes on our Homepage (located at https://www.kenscio.com) so our users know what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any time we need to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
Legal disclaimer
Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy we may need to disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our Web site.
Changes to this privacy policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.
We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the effective date at the top of this Privacy Policy.
You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.
Consent
By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.
Have questions?
Mail us at enquiries@kenscio.com
|
Subject Line - Policy and Compliance Query
Last updated September 02, 2020
This Cookie Policy explains how Kenscio Digital Marketing Pvt Ltd ("Company", "we", "us", and "our") uses cookies and similar technologies to recognize you when you visit our websites at https://www.kenscio.com, ("Websites"). It explains what these technologies are and why we use them, as well as your rights to control our use of them.
In some cases we may use cookies to collect personal information, or that becomes personal information if we combine it with other information.
What are cookies?
Cookies are small data files that are placed on your computer or mobile device when you visit a website. Cookies are widely used by website owners in order to make their websites work, or to work more efficiently, as well as to provide reporting information.
Cookies set by the website owner (in this case, Kenscio Digital Marketing Pvt Ltd) are called "first party cookies". Cookies set by parties other than the website owner are called "third party cookies". Third party cookies enable third party features or functionality to be provided on or through the website (e.g. like advertising, interactive content and analytics). The parties that set these third party cookies can recognize your computer both when it visits the website in question and also when it visits certain other websites.
Why do we use cookies?
We use first and third party cookies for several reasons. Some cookies are required for technical reasons in order for our Websites to operate, and we refer to these as "essential" or "strictly necessary" cookies. Other cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our Online Properties. Third parties serve cookies through our Websites for advertising, analytics and other purposes. This is described in more detail below.
The specific types of first and third party cookies served through our Websites and the purposes they perform are described below (please note that the specific cookies served may vary depending on the specific Online Properties you visit):
How can I control cookies?
You have the right to decide whether to accept or reject cookies. You can exercise your cookie rights by setting your preferences in the Cookie Consent Manager. The Cookie Consent Manager allows you to select which categories of cookies you accept or reject. Essential cookies cannot be rejected as they are strictly necessary to provide you with services.
The Cookie Consent Manager can be found in the notification banner and on our website. If you choose to reject cookies, you may still use our website though your access to some functionality and areas of our website may be restricted. You may also set or amend your web browser controls to accept or refuse cookies. As the means by which you can refuse cookies through your web browser controls vary from browser-to-browser, you should visit your browser's help menu for more information.
In addition, most advertising networks offer you a way to opt out of targeted advertising. If you would like to find out more information, please visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ or http://www.youronlinechoices.com.
The specific types of first and third party cookies served through our Websites and the purposes they perform are described in the table below (please note that the specific cookies served may vary depending on the specific Online Properties you visit):
Performance and functionality cookies:
These cookies are used to enhance the performance and functionality of our Websites but are non-essential to their use. However, without these cookies, certain functionality (like videos) may become unavailable.
Name:
GPS
Purpose:
A session cookie that registers a unique ID on mobile devices to enable tracking based on geographical GPS location. Expires after 30 minutes.
Provider:
youtube.com
Service:
Youtube View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
United States
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
30 minutes
Analytics and customization cookies:
These cookies collect information that is used either in aggregate form to help us understand how our Websites are being used or how effective our marketing campaigns are, or to help us customize our Websites for you.
Name:
_ga
Purpose:
It records a particular ID used to come up with data about website usage by the user. It is a HTTP cookie that expires after 2 years.
Provider:
kenscio.com
Service:
Google Analytics View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
India
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
1 year 11 months 29 days
Name:
_gid
Purpose:
Keeps an entry of unique ID which is then used to come up with statistical data on website usage by visitors. It is a HTTP cookie type and expires after a browsing session.
Provider:
kenscio.com
Service:
Google Analytics View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
India
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
1 day
Name:
_gat#
Purpose:
Enables Google Analytics regulate the rate of requesting. It is a HTTP cookie type that lasts for a session.
Provider:
kenscio.com
Service:
Google Analytics View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
India
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
1 minute
Advertising cookies:
These cookies are used to make advertising messages more relevant to you. They perform functions like preventing the same ad from continuously reappearing, ensuring that ads are properly displayed for advertisers, and in some cases selecting advertisements that are based on your interests.
Name:
VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE
Purpose:
YouTube is a Google-owned platform for hosting and sharing videos. YouTube collects user data through videos embedded in websites, which is aggregated with profile data from other Google services in order to display targeted advertising to web visitors across a broad range of their own and other websites. Used by Google in combination with SID to verify Google user account and most recent login time.
Provider:
youtube.com
Service:
YouTube View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
United States
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
5 months 27 days
Name:
YSC
Purpose:
YouTube is a Google-owned platform for hosting and sharing videos. YouTube collects user data through videos embedded in websites, which is aggregated with profile data from other Google services in order to display targeted advertising to web visitors across a broad range of their own and other websites. Used by Google in combination with SID to verify Google user account and most recent login time.
Provider:
youtube.com
Service:
YouTube View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
United States
Type:
server_cookie
Expires in:
session
Name:
test_cookie
Purpose:
A session cookie used to check if the user’s browser supports cookies.
Provider:
doubleclick.net
Service:
DoubleClick View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
United States
Type:
server_cookie
Expires in:
15 minutes
Name:
IDE
Purpose:
Used to measure the conversion rate of ads presented to the user. Expires in 1.5 years.
Provider:
doubleclick.net
Service:
DoubleClick View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
United States
Type:
server_cookie
Expires in:
1 year 11 months 29 days
What about other tracking technologies, like web beacons?
Cookies are not the only way to recognize or track visitors to a website. We may use other, similar technologies from time to time, like web beacons (sometimes called "tracking pixels" or "clear gifs"). These are tiny graphics files that contain a unique identifier that enable us to recognize when someone has visited our Websites or opened an e-mail including them. This allows us, for example, to monitor the traffic patterns of users from one page within a website to another, to deliver or communicate with cookies, to understand whether you have come to the website from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website, to improve site performance, and to measure the success of e-mail marketing campaigns. In many instances, these technologies are reliant on cookies to function properly, and so declining cookies will impair their functioning.
Do you use Flash cookies or Local Shared Objects?
Websites may also use so-called "Flash Cookies" (also known as Local Shared Objects or "LSOs") to, among other things, collect and store information about your use of our services, fraud prevention and for other site operations.
If you do not want Flash Cookies stored on your computer, you can adjust the settings of your Flash player to block Flash Cookies storage using the tools contained in the Website Storage Settings Panel. You can also control Flash Cookies by going to the Global Storage Settings Panel and following the instructions (which may include instructions that explain, for example, how to delete existing Flash Cookies (referred to "information" on the Macromedia site), how to prevent Flash LSOs from being placed on your computer without your being asked, and (for Flash Player 8 and later) how to block Flash Cookies that are not being delivered by the operator of the page you are on at the time).
Please note that setting the Flash Player to restrict or limit acceptance of Flash Cookies may reduce or impede the functionality of some Flash applications, including, potentially, Flash applications used in connection with our services or online content.
Do you serve targeted advertising?
Third parties may serve cookies on your computer or mobile device to serve advertising through our Websites. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide relevant advertisements about goods and services that you may be interested in. They may also employ technology that is used to measure the effectiveness of advertisements. This can be accomplished by them using cookies or web beacons to collect information about your visits to this and other sites in order to provide relevant advertisements about goods and services of potential interest to you. The information collected through this process does not enable us or them to identify your name, contact details or other details that directly identify you unless you choose to provide these.
How often will you update this Cookie Policy?
We may update this Cookie Policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to the cookies we use or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons. Please therefore re-visit this Cookie Policy regularly to stay informed about our use of cookies and related technologies.
The date at the top of this Cookie Policy indicates when it was last updated.
Where can I get further information?
If you have any questions about our use of cookies or other technologies, please email us at enquiries@kenscio.com or by post to:
Kenscio Digital Marketing Pvt Ltd101 Innovation, Amar Jyothi HBCS Layout, DomlurBENGALURU, India 560071India
Have questions?
Mail us at enquiries@kenscio.com
